thinktankinfo.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.thinktankinfo.com/) » Privacy Policy 

The privacy policy of Thinktank Infotech protects your information and do not disclose any of websites facts to third party. Our main goal is to deliver the information, resources and services, which are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, from time to time, we may collect information during your visits. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you learn more about the personal information we collect, who we might share it with, and how we protect it.

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy anytime and you can check out this section for the updated policies. We may store and process your information to understand your requirements and to design our products and services to suit your needs. It may also be used to provide you with information concerning our industry news, special events or features and offers suited for you.

Thinktankinfo.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about our clients. The purpose of this Privacy Statement, the word clients include visitors to our web sites, purchasers of our products, subscribers and users of our services, and advertising customers. We take your privacy very seriously and we will never sell, rent or share the information submitted on our web site. You can assure that your personal information, including your email address will be kept in strict confidence.
